meetingburner.com 2013-06-27

# 

## Privacy Statement

Your privacy is very important to us and we will treat your data with care and respect.  We know that you care how information and data about you is collected, used, and shared. This Privacy Statement describes our privacy policy and details how we collect, use, and/or disseminate the information you provide.  We reserve the right to change this Statement at any time and urge you to review our Statement regularly to familiarize yourself with any changes.

By visiting our website, using our online products/services, downloading/installing and/or using our application on a mobile phone, and/or by voluntarily submitting information to us via online forms, advertisement responses, mobile applications, and/or electronic mail, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement.

_Who We Are_

MeetingBurner has developed and licenses a subscription-based service that allows a host/presenter to share the contents of his computer monitor, his video camera, and his voice with other participants.  All of this is conducted via the internet and/or with our optional phone bridge add-on.  The host can configure his account so that participants can see a logo, a picture of the presenter, meeting information, participant lists, or other information as the host/presenter chooses.  In addition, we allow the participants to ask electronic questions of the host.

Due to the fact that each online meeting is controlled by an independent host/presenter, we cannot guarantee how the system and privacy information will be managed by the independent host/presenter.

To provide the service, we may be required to collect, use, and share certain information. The type of information we collect, together with a description of how we use and/or share it, is described below.

**Information Collection and Use**

**Information Collection**  
MeetingBurner, our partners, and the independent presenter/host who subscribes to MeetingBurner are the owners of the information collected on our site.

Registration  
In order to use the site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as, username and password), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

Order  
We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

**Information Use**

We will use personal information that we gather about you to provide the services that you have requested. In addition, if you have a free account with MeetingBurner, then we will use the information gathered about you to share more information about our business in an attempt to convince you to make a purchase from us or our associated companies. MeetingBurner and, if you are a participant in a online meeting, the host/presenter who sent you to this site, will be granted access to your personal contact (name, phone number, and email) information so that they can communicate with you in an attempt to "sell" various products, services, and memberships to you.

**Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do share your profile with other third parties. Your profile is shared together with your personally identifiable information. YOUR PAYMENT INFORMATION IS NEVER SHARED FOR ANY REASON WITH ANY OUTSIDE THIRD PARTY UNLESS REQUIRED BY LAW.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the 'Profile' section.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons, Web Bugs, CSS, and similar functionality)**  
We employ or our third party advertising company employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are tied to users' personally identifiable information.

Clear Gifs can "work with" existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same Web site or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited 'www.companyX.com', which uses an advertising company's clear gif, the Web site or advertising company would match the clear gif's identifier and the advertising company's cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information would then be given to the advertising company or Web site.

In addition, we use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section. 

**Communications from the Site**  
Special Offers and Updates  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter.

Service Announcements  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

Customer Service  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Sharing**  
Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Third Party Advertisers:  
We may use the information you have voluntarily provided to cause information, offers, products, and/or services that appear to us to be consistent with your expressed interests to be directed to you. This is typically accomplished by using your information to direct to you information, offers, products, and/or services from us and/or one of our affiliated companies. Your information may, therefore, ultimately be used for marketing purposes by us, our affiliated companies, and/or any one or more of the associated businesses with which we work, or by the host/presenter of an event. 

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

After we share your information with our affiliated companies and/or any of the several businesses with which we work, or with the host/presenter of an event in which you have chosen to participate, we lose control over how they will use, collect, and/or disseminate your information. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the Privacy Statements of the corresponding affiliated companies with whom we have shared your information in order to acquaint yourself with their information collection, use, and/or sharing policies. 

You understand and agree that MeetingBurner is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the host/presenter and/or these other websites, and you agree that MeetingBurner is not responsible for how such information is ultimately used.

**These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information :**  
We Share Personal Contact Information with third parties, including the host/presenter of an event. If you want to ensure that your information is never shared with any third party, you must request to be unsubscribed or cancelled from our service. Failure to unsubscribe or cancel your service will imply that you are interested in having your personal information shared with various third parties.

Third Party Intermediaries  
We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Service Providers  
We partner with other third parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services and for purposes referenced in their privacy policies.

Business Transitions  
In the event MeetingBurner goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site only by completely opting-out of our service and/or canceling a paid subscription to our service.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the unsubscribe instructions sent with every email. 

**Links**  
This Web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, MeetingBurner, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Children's privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the young is important to us. Therefore, you cannot use this site if you are not 18 years old. If you are not 18 years old, you are not permitted to access this website for any reason. Because of this, we never knowingly collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 18.

**Telecommunications privacy** Protecting the privacy of your telecommunications information is important to us. When members or prospects make phone calls to telecommunication services provided by us, we may track information about the name, phone number, and other information about the calling party. In addition, we may gather information about telecommunication services used by our members. By contacting us via telephone you are allowing us to contact you even if your phone number is on any legal DNC (do not call) lists. 

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, we strive to ensure that their information is protected both online and off-line. However, please be aware that no data transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just "surfing".

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a secure facility.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to support@meetingburner.com.

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

**Enhancement of Marketing Profile**  
We may purchase third party marketing data and add it to our existing user database to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers we think our users would be interested in. We use this information to enhance or overlay the "profile" of individual users. This aggregate marketing data is therefore tied to the users' personally identifiable information. See also the 'Profile'.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), if a user no longer wishes to use our service, or otherwises wishes to review the user's personally identifiable information, a user may review, correct, update, or delete/deactivate the user's personally identifiable information by logging in to the user's account, or for additional assistance, by contacting support at support@meetingburner.com

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement in places that we deem appropriate. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: support@meetingburner.com

**This policy is effective January 14, 2013**
